caixinglobal.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Caixin

Caixin Media Limited and its affiliates are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users. We want you to be familiar with how we collect, use and protect information from and about you, which applies to all Caixin platforms including our websites, mobile sites, applications ("apps"), and electronic newsletters.

**What information Caixin collects from users**

We only collect your personal information of your own accord. The data that we collect may include name, address, email address, etc. We may also collect information that we request from you regarding your use of our service, surveys and registrations to our events or that we obtain automatically about your visit to our digital platforms, such as page views, scrolling, and text entered.

**How Caixin uses the information?**

-To provide services.

We use the information we collect from and about you to process orders, fulfill subscription, send information about transactions with us, and so on. We may also use your information to contact you, such as responding to your comments, inquiries or requests. If you want to stop receiving these materials from us, you can write to us.

-To perform statistical analysis.

We occasionally conduct market research surveys and provide reports to our clients about usage under corporate licenses. We provide statistical, demographic and marketing analyses of users of Caixin, and their subscribing and purchasing patterns, for product upgrading purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our user base.

-To deliver relevant recommendations.

We may periodically send promotional materials, surveys, or notifications related to our content, events, products and services. We may also run competitions and prize draws.

**With whom we share the information**

If you have registered to use Caixin services, we will not sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your email address without your permission. In the future, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, we may include your information among the transferred assets.

We may allow Caixin’s subsidiary media and services to use your contact information for promotion and recommendation if you choose to receive them.

We maintain the rights to provide user information including but not limited to the following conditions: when a law or regulation requires, when we have to preserve our integrity and legality, when we respond to your request, when we cooperate with investigation for public securities concerns.

**User access and control of data**

You may update and/or edit your personal information at any time. You can email or call us for help.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files which a website may put on your computer or mobile device when you first visit a site or page. The cookie will help the website, or another website, to recognize your device the next time you visit, the number of visits you have paid, or the activities you have made on the digital platforms. We may use cookies and other tracking technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies) when you visit or use Caixin. Third parties that support Caixin by serving advertisements or providing services, such as providing users with the ability to comment on content, allowing users to share content, customizing content based on usage, or tracking aggregate site usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect information on Caixin platforms.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether, but that may limit the services we are able to provide to you.

**Access to other websites**

We may put links to other websites on Caixin platforms. When you access other websites, please refer to the privacy policy released there. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any websites other than Caixin and its subsidiaries. Once you leave Caixin platforms or click an advertisement, or sign up for a special offer, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the other service.

**Changes to Caixin Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may modify this Privacy Policy. We will post the latest version on this page and we suggest you access it occasionally because we will not notify you on any updates. We will not change the old way of collecting and using information before the change is made.
